[
    {
        "Article category": "World",
        "Headline": "Kenyan Authorities Say Son of Official Was Among Gunmen in University Attack",
        "Author": "Jeffrey Gettleman and Isma’il Kushkush",
        "Date": "4/5/15",
        "C-deck": "The identification of one of the gunmen in the attack that killed nearly 150 students as the son of a local chief near the Somali border rekindled fears of a homegrown terrorism problem.",
        "URL": "http://www.nytimes.com/2015/04/06/world/africa/kenyan-authorities-say-son-of-official-was-among-gunmen-in-university-attack.html",
        "Question": "Abdirahim Abdullahi, one of the gunmen in the Kenyan university attack, quit his job at a Nairobi bank to do which of the following?",
        "Correct answer": "Become part of the Shabab Islamist militant group",
        "Incorrect answer A": "Go back to school at the University of Nairobi",
        "Incorrect answer B": "Attend Garissa University College",
        "Incorrect answer C": "Join the Boko Haram Islamist militant group"
    },
    {
        "Article category": "World",
        "Headline": "Bulgaria Puts Up a New Wall, but This One Keeps People Out",
        "Author": "Rick Lyman",
        "Date": "4/5/15",
        "C-deck": "The former Communist nation has completed 20 miles of fence along its border with Turkey, and plans to extend it to 100 miles, to stem the flow of refugees.",
        "URL": "http://www.nytimes.com/2015/04/06/world/europe/bulgaria-puts-up-a-new-wall-but-this-one-keeps-people-out.html",
        "Question": "Which of the following is NOT a reason why Bulgaria wants to build a fence along the Turkish border?",
        "Correct answer": "To encourage its citizens to remain in the country",
        "Incorrect answer A": "To end problems caused by the country's surge in immigration",
        "Incorrect answer B": "To reduce the likelihood of jihadists and foreign fighters entering the country",
        "Incorrect answer C": "To demonstrate that it should become part of the Schengen group of nations"
    },
    {
        "Article category": "World",
        "Headline": "Taking Feminist Battle to China's Streets, and Landing in Jail",
        "Author": "Andrew Jacobs",
        "Date": "4/5/15",
        "C-deck": "The detention of five outspoken activists, part of an effort to quash the nascent feminist movement, is seen as a dismal milestone in the Communist Party's war on grass-roots activism.",
        "URL": "http://www.nytimes.com/2015/04/06/world/asia/chinese-womens-rights-activists-fall-afoul-of-officials.html",
        "Question": "Five Chinese women are in jail because they were accused of provoking social instability. What were they planning when they were arrested?",
        "Correct answer": "A public awareness campaign about sexual harassment on public transportation",
        "Incorrect answer A": "A protest about inequality in higher education",
        "Incorrect answer B": "A demonstration about the indignities women face while waiting in line for the restroom",
        "Incorrect answer C": "A protest about the government's treatment of the LGBTQ community"
    },
    {
        "Article category": "U.S.",
        "Headline": "Battling Crime and Calories at F.B.I. (Fit Bureau of Investigation)",
        "Author": "Michael S. Schmidt",
        "Date": "4/5/15",
        "C-deck": "New fitness tests are in part a response to increasing concerns of senior F.B.I. officials about the toll on agents after the attacks of Sept. 11, 2001.",
        "URL": "http://www.nytimes.com/2015/04/06/us/battling-crime-and-calories-at-fbi-fit-bureau-of-investigation.html",
        "Question": "FBI Director James B. Comey thought that reinstating the bureau's mandatory fitness test would emphasize the important of all of the following EXCEPT:",
        "Correct answer": "Outrunning an enemy",
        "Incorrect answer A": "Fitness",
        "Incorrect answer B": "Stress management",
        "Incorrect answer C": "Work-life balance"
    },
    {
        "Article category": "U.S.",
        "Headline": "70 Years On, Crowd Gets Close to the Birthplace of the Atomic Bomb",
        "Author": "Rick Rojas",
        "Date": "4/5/15",
        "C-deck": "Seventy years after the first test of the atomic bomb, tourists flock to the New Mexican desert.",
        "URL": "http://www.nytimes.com/2015/04/06/us/70-years-on-crowd-gets-close-to-the-birthplace-of-the-atomic-bomb.html",
        "Question": "What is the birthplace of the atomic bomb known as?",
        "Correct answer": "Trinity Site",
        "Incorrect answer A": "Area 51",
        "Incorrect answer B": "Testing Site B",
        "Incorrect answer C": "Uncharted territory"
    },
    {
        "Article category": "U.S.",
        "Headline": "California Seeks to Make Way for Statue of Sally Ride in U.S. Capitol",
        "Author": "Carol Pogash",
        "Date": "4/5/15",
        "C-deck": "If legislators have their way, the statue will replace that of the Rev. Junipero Serra, the 18th-century Catholic priest, in the National Statuary Hall Collection in Washington.",
        "URL": "http://www.nytimes.com/2015/04/06/us/california-seeks-to-make-way-for-statue-of-sally-ride-in-the-nations-capitol.html",
        "Question": "Which statue would California have to get rid of before it could build a statue of Sally Ride in the U.S. Capitol?",
        "Correct answer": "The Rev. Junipero Serra",
        "Incorrect answer A": "Thomas Starr King",
        "Incorrect answer B": "Ronald Reagan",
        "Incorrect answer C": "Arnold Schwarzenegger"
    },
    {
        "Article category": "Politics",
        "Headline": "In Chicago’s Reshaped Politics, Unions Are Divided Over Mayoral Race",
        "Author": "Monica Davey",
        "Date": "4/5/15",
        "C-deck": "Labor is vital to the chances of Jesus G. Garcia in Tuesday's runoff. But Mayor Rahm Emanuel is receiving a surprisingly solid amount of union support.",
        "URL": "http://www.nytimes.com/2015/04/06/us/in-chicagos-reshaped-politics-unions-are-divided-over-mayoral-race.html",
        "Question": "Chicago mayoral candidate Jesus \"Chuy\" Garcia built his campaign on the backing of whom?",
        "Correct answer": "Teachers",
        "Incorrect answer A": "Fast-food workers",
        "Incorrect answer B": "Construction workers",
        "Incorrect answer C": "Public works employees"
    },
    {
        "Article category": "Politics",
        "Headline": "O’Hare Noise Complaints Influence Chicago’s Mayoral Race",
        "Author": "Mitch Smith",
        "Date": "4/5/15",
        "C-deck": "Mounting frustration, and what some perceive as indifference from City Hall, has made plane noise a subplot in Tuesday's runoff election.",
        "URL": "http://www.nytimes.com/2015/04/06/us/ohare-noise-complaints-influence-chicagos-mayoral-race.html",
        "Question": "Chicago Mayor Rahm Emanuel says he has done all EXCEPT what in response to the noise complaints surrounding O'Hare International Airport?",
        "Correct answer": "Talked with O'Hare employees",
        "Incorrect answer A": "Met with concerned residents",
        "Incorrect answer B": "Installed noise monitors",
        "Incorrect answer C": "Urged the FAA to speed up a process that would help residents pay for additional insulation"
    },
    {
        "Article category": "Politics",
        "Headline": "Wisconsin Supreme Court Election Raises Concerns About Partisanship",
        "Author": "Mitch Smith",
        "Date": "4/5/15",
        "C-deck": "Ahead of the vote on Tuesday, out-of-state money has poured in, and harsh advertisements have filled the airwaves.",
        "URL": "http://www.nytimes.com/2015/04/06/us/wisconsin-supreme-court-election-raises-partisanship-concerns.html",
        "Question": "Who is the incumbent seeking a third term in the Wisconsin Supreme Court election?",
        "Correct answer": "Ann Walsh Bradley",
        "Incorrect answer A": "James Daley",
        "Incorrect answer B": "Shirley S. Abrahamson",
        "Incorrect answer C": "Amber Wichowsky"
    },
    {
        "Article category": "Business",
        "Headline": "RadioShack’s Blueprint for a Rebirth, Planned by a Hedge Fund",
        "Author": "Hiroko Tabuchi",
        "Date": "4/5/15",
        "C-deck": "Standard General, which will take over 1,700 of the 4,000 RadioShack stores, said that eliminating the retailer's heavy cost structure and some old business practices left a core worth saving.",
        "URL": "http://www.nytimes.com/2015/04/06/business/radioshacks-blueprint-for-a-rebirth-planned-by-a-hedge-fund.html",
        "Question": "Which hedge fund is taking over 1,700 RadioShack stores?",
        "Correct answer": "Standard General",
        "Incorrect answer A": "Customer Growth Partners",
        "Incorrect answer B": "Salus Capital Partners",
        "Incorrect answer C": "Citadel"
    },
    {
        "Article category": "Business",
        "Headline": "China Escalates Hollywood Partnerships, Aiming to Compete One Day",
        "Author": "David Barboza",
        "Date": "4/5/15",
        "C-deck": "Chinese studios are helping develop, design and produce world-class animated features and have ambitions to go global with their own.",
        "URL": "http://www.nytimes.com/2015/04/06/business/media/china-escalates-hollywood-partnerships-aiming-to-compete-one-day.html",
        "Question": "What movie marks the first collaboration between DreamWorks Studios and Oriental DreamWorks, its Chinese counterpart?",
        "Correct answer": "\"Kung Fu Panda 3\"",
        "Incorrect answer A": "\"The Hunger Games: Mockingjay, Part 2\"",
        "Incorrect answer B": "\"Avengers: Age of Ultron\"",
        "Incorrect answer C": "\"Insidious: Chapter 3\""
    },
    {
        "Article category": "Business",
        "Headline": "Greece and I.M.F. Hold Talks on Crucial Debt Payment",
        "Author": "Landon Thomas Jr.",
        "Date": "4/5/15",
        "C-deck": "Greece's finance minister, Yanis Varoufakis, and the International Monetary Fund's chief, Christine Lagarde, met in Washington as the due date neared for a 458 million euro payment to the fund.",
        "URL": "http://www.nytimes.com/2015/04/06/business/international/greece-and-imf-hold-talks-on-crucial-debt-payment.html",
        "Question": "How much money (in euros) must Greece pay the International Monetary Fund on April 9?",
        "Correct answer": "458 million euros",
        "Incorrect answer A": "548 million euros",
        "Incorrect answer B": "485 million euros",
        "Incorrect answer C": "584 million euros"
    },
    {
        "Article category": "Technology",
        "Headline": "Publication of New Internet Rules to Prompt Cheers and Challenges",
        "Author": "Rebecca R. Ruiz  ",
        "Date": "4/5/15",
        "C-deck": "The F.C.C. regulations are expected to appear in the Federal Register as early as this week, starting two 60-day countdowns: one until they take effect and the other until a deadline for lawsuits.",
        "URL": "http://bits.blogs.nytimes.com/2015/04/05/publication-of-net-neutrality-rules-to-prompt-cheers-and-challenges/",
        "Question": "New Internet regulations approved in February will forbid all of the following except:",
        "Correct answer": "Searching online for pornographic materials",
        "Incorrect answer A": "Speeding up access to particular content",
        "Incorrect answer B": "Slowing down access to particular content",
        "Incorrect answer C": "Blocking access to particular content"
    },
    {
        "Article category": "Technology",
        "Headline": "Online Test-Takers Feel Anti-Cheating Software’s Uneasy Glare",
        "Author": "Natasha Singer",
        "Date": "4/5/15",
        "C-deck": "School administrators say for online learning to be legitimate, testing has to be monitored. Proctortrack is a new anti-cheating program being used by some universities.",
        "URL": "http://www.nytimes.com/2015/04/06/technology/online-test-takers-feel-anti-cheating-softwares-uneasy-glare.html",
        "Question": "Which of the following is a software used to administer online testing?",
        "Correct answer": "Proctortrack",
        "Incorrect answer A": "Stoplight",
        "Incorrect answer B": "Turnitin",
        "Incorrect answer C": "Testtaker"
    },
    {
        "Article category": "Technology",
        "Headline": "Iran Is Raising Sophistication and Frequency of Cyberattacks, Study Says",
        "Author": "David E. Sanger and Nicole Perlroth",
        "Date": "4/15/15",
        "C-deck": "A new study concludes that Iran has greatly increased the frequency and skill of its cyberattacks, even while negotiating with world powers over its nuclear program.",
        "URL": "http://www.nytimes.com/2015/04/16/world/middleeast/iran-is-raising-sophistication-and-frequency-of-cyberattacks-study-says.html",
        "Question": "What have Iran's cyberattacks on the U.S. mostly involved?",
        "Correct answer": "Espionage",
        "Incorrect answer A": "Destruction",
        "Incorrect answer B": "Oil theft",
        "Incorrect answer C": "Religious attacks"
    },
    {
        "Article category": "Sports",
        "Headline": "UConn Too Big, Too Savvy and Too Much for Upstart Maryland",
        "Author": "Harvey Araton",
        "Date": "4/5/15",
        "C-deck": "The Huskies and Coach Geno Auriemma, who are no strangers to the Final Four or the N.C.A.A. women's championship game, will play Notre Dame on Tuesday.",
        "URL": "http://www.nytimes.com/2015/04/06/sports/ncaabasketball/connecticut-defeats-maryland-earning-chance-to-play-for-a-10th-ncaa-title.html",
        "Question": "Before this season, how many consecutive national titles had the Connecticut women's basketball team won?",
        "Correct answer": "Two",
        "Incorrect answer A": "One",
        "Incorrect answer B": "Three",
        "Incorrect answer C": "None"
    },
    {
        "Article category": "Sports",
        "Headline": "Notre Dame Stifles South Carolina’s Gritty Rally to Reach Second Straight Final",
        "Author": "Jonathan Czupryn",
        "Date": "4/5/15",
        "C-deck": "For the second season in a row and the fourth time in five years, the Irish will play for the women's national basketball championship.",
        "URL": "http://www.nytimes.com/2015/04/06/sports/ncaabasketball/notre-dame-defeats-south-carolina-to-advance-to-second-straight-ncaa-title-game.html",
        "Question": "Who did Notre Dame's women's basketball team play after it beat South Carolina in the national semifinal?",
        "Correct answer": "Connecticut",
        "Incorrect answer A": "Duke",
        "Incorrect answer B": "Wisconsin",
        "Incorrect answer C": "Kansas"
    },
    {
        "Article category": "Sports",
        "Headline": "Track’s Heartbeat Is Fast as Ever in Jamaica",
        "Author": "Michael Powell",
        "Date": "4/5/15",
        "C-deck": "In Jamaica, whether the races feature Usain Bolt or a group of teenagers, running is a national obsession.",
        "URL": "http://www.nytimes.com/2015/04/06/sports/tracks-heartbeat-is-fast-as-ever-in-jamaica.html",
        "Question": "What is the name of the Jamaica's five-day high school track competition?",
        "Correct answer": "Champs",
        "Incorrect answer A": "Gold",
        "Incorrect answer B": "Jamaica Open",
        "Incorrect answer C": "National Race"
    }
]